<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-30T16:34:17-06:00</updated><id>https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Danish Cookies</title><subtitle>Mati Danish's blog</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Project Planning</title><link href="https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/2023/01/30/Project-planning.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Project Planning" /><published>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-30T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/2023/01/30/Project-planning</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Features: Taiyo - product cards and filters and different brands Luna - Email subscription, Formatting of the website Ethan - Heart function Mati - Log in button and and the sign up button Aaron - Notes On Mort’s discussion Beneficial and Harmful effects of Computing: Delivery Military Spying Causing destruction by flying into something Chat GPT was sponsored by Microsoft and now has 10 billion dollars since they think its the google killer. The GPT saves from the secondary clicking, don’t know the source (cite sources). Good because you can answer right away. Computer bias - worry ab using the computers, inserting own bias into the computers Community dev did have the test space to make for all other people (HP facial scanning) didn’t test on enough different people One mind and one thought process Are you inserting your own Bias? (make sure not to exempt other perspectives) Asb Club Spreadsheet Notes: Frontend: The speaker presents an overview and purpose for their website/app The frontend is described and the future implementations and functions are discussed Backend: Describes how the database will be used Shows a backend Model, View, and Control flow Describes the relationship between the users and the database Basic overview of the website, ie. the different pages Shows planner, for this part I think it would be beneficial to show the scrum board we already have Briefly goes over an example of the issues on the Scrum Board Finishes the presentation with a manifesto Confirm active clubs: Allow club leadership to update information on their own website Features and design: Club info database Anyone viewing the website can see the database However, only people with “admin” can interact with the page Database with each club: There are reviews for each club so students wanting to join different clubs can see different input on different clubs. Each club can have many reviews The upload files feature allows club leadership to submit necessary files to a database that allows ASB administrators to view and confirm files. Club search feature: search a topic of interest and you will get a club with that interest]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unit 3 Sections 8 and 10</title><link href="https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/lesson%20plans/2023/01/29/team-3-hacks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unit 3 Sections 8 and 10" /><published>2023-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/lesson%20plans/2023/01/29/team-3-hacks</id><author><name></name></author><category term="lesson plans" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[During this lesson sections 5 and 7 will discuss lists and iteration]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unit 3.9 &amp;amp; 3.11 Hacks</title><link href="https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/trimester%202%20student%20teaching/2023/01/29/t5-hacks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unit 3.9 &amp;amp; 3.11 Hacks" /><published>2023-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/trimester%202%20student%20teaching/2023/01/29/t5-hacks</id><author><name></name></author><category term="trimester 2 student teaching" /><category term="hacks" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">t4</title><link href="https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/t4" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="t4" /><published>2023-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-29T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/T4-hacks</id><author><name></name></author><category term="hacks" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[t4]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Digital Divide</title><link href="https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/Digi_Divi" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Digital Divide" /><published>2023-01-23T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-01-23T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://hsinaditam.github.io/Danish_Cookies/Digital-Divide</id><author><name></name></author><category term="blogs" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three beneficial effect:]]></summary></entry></feed>